Finding aid to Buildings records CA.MS.00104
Smith College Archives
- Museum of Art-Exhibits
  - -1987-1988 (Box 251.1, Folder 14)
  - -1988-1989 (Box 251.1, Folder 15)
  - -1989-1990 (Box 251.1, Folder 16)
  - -1989-1990-Baroque Painters in Italy (Box 251.1, Folder 17)
  - -1989-1990-Clippings (Box 251.1, Folder 18)
  - -1990-1991 (Box 251.2, Folder 1)
  - -1990-1991-Clippings (Box 251.2, Folder 2)
  - -1991-1992 (Box 251.2, Folder 3)
  - -1991-1992-Clippings (Box 251.2, Folder 4)
  - -1992-1993 (Box 251.2, Folder 5)
  - -1992-1993-Clippings (Box 251.2, Folder 6)
  - -1993-1994 (Box 251.2, Folder 7)
  - -1993-1994-Clippings (Box 251.2, Folder 8)
  - -1994-1995 (Box 251.2, Folder 9)
  - -1994-1995-Clippings (Box 251.2, Folder 10)
  - -1995-1996 (Box 251.2, Folder 11)
  - -1995-1996-Clippings (Box 251.2, Folder 12)
  - -1996-1997 (Box 251.2, Folder 13)
  - -1996-1997-Clippings (Box 251.2, Folder 14)
  - -1997-1998 (Box 251.2, Folder 15)
  - -1997-1998-Clippings (Box 251.2, Folder 16)
  - -1998-1999 (Box 251.2, Folder 17)
  - -1998-1999-Clippings (Box 251.2, Folder 18)
  - -1999-2000 (Box 251.2, Folder 19)
  - -1999-2000-Clippings (Box 251.2, Folder 20)
  - -2002- (Box 251.3)
- Museum of Art-A Guide to the Collections, 1986
- Museum of Art-Bulletin Nos. 1-11, 1912-1930 (Box 251.4)
- Museum of Art-Bulletin Nos. 12-20, 1930-1939 (Box 251.4)
- Museum of Art-Bulletin Nos. 21-32, 1939-1951 (Box 251.4)
- Museum of Art-Bulletin Nos. 33-39, 1952-1959 (Box 251.4)
- Northrop House
  [see also Gillett House]
  - -General, 1912- (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - -Banners, undated (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - -History, 1935-1942 (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1911-; undated (Box 252, Folder 4)
    - -Exterior-Porch, undated (Box 252, Folder 5)
    - -Interior, 1918-; undated (Box 252, Folder 6)
    - -Groups, 1916-; undated (Box 252, Folder 7)
- Oak House
  - -General, 1987-1991 (Box 252, Folder 8)
  - -Clippings, 1980-1992 (Box 252, Folder 9)
  - -Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 252, Folder 10)
  - -Photographs-Exterior, 1977-1990 (Box 252, Folder 11)
  - -Photographs-Groups, 1977-1990 (Box 252, Folder 12)
- Observatory
  - -General, 1886-1956 (Box 252.1, Folder 1)
  - -Bookplate
  - -Clock, undated (Box 252.1, Folder 2)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1877-1900 (Box 252.1, Folder 3)
    - -Exterior, 1901-1960 (Box 252.1, Folder 4)
    - -Exterior, undated (Box 252.1, Folder 5)
    - -Exterior-With Other Buildings, 1911-1960 (Box 252.1, Folder 6)
    - -Interior, 1904-1960 (Box 252.1, Folder 7)
  - -Sketches and Drawings (Artistic), undated (Box 252.1, Folder 8)
- Observatory-Whately Observatory, undated (Box 252.1, Folder 9)
- Owl's Nest
- Paradise Road
  - -# 7
    [see Jordan House Annex]
  - -# 8
  - -# 58, 1939-1977 (Box 252.1, Folder 10)
  - -# 61 (Mandelle Annex), 1940; undated (Box 252.1, Folder 11)
  - -# 66, undated (Box 252.1, Folder 12)
- Park Group, 2001 (Box 252.2, Folder 1)
- Park House
  - -General, 1938- (Box 252.2, Folder 2)
  - -Artifacts
  - -Finances
    - -General, 1976-1977 (Box 252.2, Folder 3)
    - -Bills and Receipts, 1975-1976 (Box 252.2, Folder 4)
    - -Bills and Receipts, 1977 (Box 252.2, Folder 5)
    - -Deposit and Withdrawal Slips, 1972-1976 (Box 252.2, Folder 6)
  - -Histories, 1924-1952 (Box 252.2, Folder 7)
  - -House President's Notebook, 1953-1971 (Box 252.2, Folder 8)
  - -House President's Notebook, 1977-1979 (Box 252.2, Folder 9)
  - -Roster / Register, 1924-1955 (Box 252.2, Folder 10)
  - -Roster / Register, 1955-1981 (Box 252.2, Folder 11)
  - -Scripts for Skits and Plays, 1967-1968 (Box 252.2, Folder 12)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1923-; undated (Box 252.2, Folder 13)
    - -Interior, 1924-; undated (Box 252.2, Folder 14)
    - -Groups, 1912-1950 (Box 253, Folder 1)
    - -Groups, 1950- (Box 253, Folder 2)
    - -Groups-House Photo Album, 1962 (Box 253, Folder 3)
    - -Groups (Box 253)
- Park House Annex
  - -General, 1972- (Box 253, Folder 4)
  - -Photographs-Exterior, 1937- (Box 253, Folder 5)
  - -Photographs-Groups, 1963- (Box 253, Folder 6)
- Parking Garage, 1998- (Box 253, Folder 7)
- Parsons House
  - -General, 1946- (Box 253, Folder 8)
  - -Disasters, 1980- (Box 253, Folder 9)
  - -Histories, 1922-1953 (Box 253, Folder 10)
  - -Roster / Register, 1923-1951 (Box 253, Folder 11)
  - -Roster / Register, 1952-1969 (Box 253, Folder 12)
  - -Social Chair's Book, 1952-1955 (Box 253, Folder 13)
  - -Social Chair's Book, 1956-1957 (Box 253, Folder 14)
  - -Social Chair's Book, 1958-1963 (Box 253, Folder 15)
  - -Social Chair's Book, 1964-1965 (Box 253, Folder 16)
  - -Social Chair's Book, 1966-1967 (Box 253, Folder 17)
  - -Social Chair's Book, 1968-1969 (Box 253, Folder 18)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1910- (Box 253, Folder 19)
    - -Groups, 1915-1939 (Box 253.1, Folder 1)
    - -Groups, 1940- (Box 253.1, Folder 2)
    - -Groups (Box 253.1)
- Parsons House Annex (25 Henshaw Avenue and 19 Round Hill Road), 1966- (Box 253.1, Folder 3)
  [see also Hover House]
- The Perch
- Physical Plant
  [see West Street # 125]
- Pierce Hall
  - -General, 1882- (Box 253.1, Folder 4)
  - -Artifacts
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior-Campus View, 1882- (Box 253.1, Folder 5)
    - -Exterior-West St. View, 1882 (Box 253.1, Folder 6)
    - -Exterior (Box 253.1)
    - -Interior, undated (Box 253.1, Folder 7)
    - -McCallum House (site of Pierce Hall), undated (Box 253.1)
- Plymouth Hall / Inn, 1896-1989 (Box 253.1, Folder 9)
- Plymouth Hall / Inn-Photographs, 1896-1935 (Box 253.1, Folder 10)
- Pomeroy House (36 Bedford Terrace), 1901-1980; undated (Box 253.1, Folder 11)
- President's House
  - -General, 1921- (Box 254, Folder 1)
  - -Kitchen and Serving Facilities, 1951- (Box 254, Folder 2)
  - -Kneeland Home
    - -General, 1997 (Box 254, Folder 3)
    - -Garden Book, 1881-1912 (Box 254, Folder 4)
    - -Garden Book, 1900-1915 (Box 254, Folder 5)
    - -Guest Book, 1904-1919 (Box 254, Folder 6)
    - -Photographs, undated (Box 254, Folder 7)
    - -Photographs-Album, undated (Box 254, Folder 8)
  - -Miscellaneous, 1933- (Box 254, Folder 9)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior-Front, 1920-; undated (Box 254.1, Folder 1)
    - -Exterior-Rear, undated (Box 254.1, Folder 2)
    - -Exterior-Rear-from Pond, 1942- (Box 254.1, Folder 3)
    - -Exterior-Rear-Terrace, undated (Box 254.1, Folder 4)
    - -Exterior-Side, undated (Box 254.1, Folder 5)
    - -Exterior-Special Features, 1942- (Box 254.1, Folder 6)
    - -Interior, 1920- (Box 254.1, Folder 7)
- Prospect Street # 10
  - -General, 1929-1981; undated (Box 254.1, Folder 8)
  - -Blueprint for Kitchen, undated (Box 254.1, Folder 9)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1930-1953; undated (Box 254.1, Folder 10)
    - -Interior, undated (Box 254.1, Folder 11)
    - -Gardens, 1930-1977; undated (Box 254.1, Folder 12)
- Quadrangle
  [see also Comstock House, Cushing House, Ellen Emerson House, Gardiner House, Franklin King House, Jordan House, Laura Scales House, Morrow House, Wilder House, and Wilson House]
  - -General, 1922- (Box 254.1, Folder 13)
  - -Photographs
    - -General, 1930- (Box 254.1, Folder 14)
    - -General, undated (Box 254.1, Folder 15)
    - -Aerial Views, undated (Box 254.1, Folder 16)
    - -Events, 1948- (Box 254.1, Folder 17)
  - -Sketches, Drawings, and Models (Architectural), undated (Box 254.1, Folder 18)
- Quadrangle-Mandelle Quadrangle
  [see also Comstock House and Wilder House]
  - -General, 1929- (Box 255, Folder 1)
  - -Architectural Plans, 1929 (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - -Ewing Memorial Steps, 1925- (Box 255, Folder 3)
  - -Mary S. Mandelle, 1930 (Box 255, Folder 4)
  - -Photographs-Exterior-Front Views, 1930- (Box 255, Folder 5)
  - -Photographs-Exterior-Other Views, 1930- (Box 255, Folder 6)
- The Quill
- Quimby House
  [see Dawes House (18 Henshaw Avenue)]
- The Rosemont
  [see Bedford Terrace #6]
- Round Hill Road
  - -# 19
    [see Parsons Annex]
  - -# 83, 1892 (Box 255, Folder 7)
- Sage Hall
  - -General, 1924- (Box 255, Folder 8)
  - -Rededication
    [see box 102, folder 11a and Flat File Drawer 9 (Appendix H) for poster]
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1924- (Box 255, Folder 9)
    - -Exterior, undated (Box 255, Folder 10)
    - -Exterior
    - -Interior and Special Features, 1924 (Box 255, Folder 11)
    - -Rededication Ceremony, April 1991 (Box 255, Folder 11a)
  - -Sketches and Drawings (Architectural and Artistic), 1924 (Box 255, Folder 12)
- Science Center
  - -Bass Hall
    - -General, 1990- (Box 255, Folder 13)
    - -Dedication
      [see Flat File Drawer 9 (Appendix H) for poster]
    - -Scrapbook, 1992
    - -Young Science Library
      [see Libraries-Young Science Library]
  - -Burton Hall
    [see Burton Hall and Clark Science Center]
  - -Clark Science Center
    - -General, 1966- (Box 255, Folder 14)
    - -Addition / Renovation Plan, 1989 (Box 255, Folder 15)
      [see also Flat File Drawer 9 (Appendix H) for original and renovation plans]
    - -Brochures, undated (Box 255, Folder 16)
    - -Clippings and Press Releases, 1962- (Box 255, Folder 17)
    - -Equipment, 1966- (Box 255, Folder 18)
    - -McConnell Hall
      - -General, 1966- (Box 256, Folder 1)
      - -Computer Center, 1968-1994 (Box 256, Folder 2)
      - -Computer Center-Newsletter, 1982-1983 (Box 256, Folder 3)
      - -Foucault's Pendulum, 1980- (Box 256, Folder 4)
    - -National Science Foundation Proposal, 1963 (Box 256, Folder 5)
      - -Official Opening (Box 256)
      - -General, May 1967 (Box 256, Folder 6)
      - -Press-Clippings and Press Releases, Jan-May 1967 (Box 256, Folder 7)
      - -Press-Correspondence and Memoranda, Jan-May 1967 (Box 256, Folder 8)
      - -Speakers, 1967 (Box 256, Folder 9)
      - -Speakers-Bronowski and Horton, 1967 (Box 256, Folder 10)
      - -Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 256, Folder 11)
      - -Photographs, May 1967 (Box 256, Folder 12)
    - -Physical Plant Development Program, 1962 (Box 256, Folder 13)
    - -Plans, 1966 (Box 256, Folder 14)
    - -Regulations, 1967- (Box 256, Folder 15)
    - -Regulations-Safety, 1973- (Box 256, Folder 16)
    - -Sabin-Reed Hall
      [see Clark Science Center-General and see Libraries-Sabin-Reed Science Library]
    - -Women in Science Summer Program, 1991 (Box 256, Folder 17)
    - -Women in Science Summer Program, 1993 (Box 256, Folder 18)
    - -Photographs
      - -Exterior, undated (Box 255.1, Folder 1)
      - -Exterior-Bridge and Courtyard, 1966- (Box 255.1, Folder 2)
      - -Exterior-Burton and Sabin-Reed, undated (Box 255.1, Folder 3)
      - -Exterior-McConnell Hall, undated (Box 255.1, Folder 4)
      - -Interior-Burton and Sabin-Reed, 1969- (Box 255.1, Folder 5)
      - -Interior-McConnell, undated (Box 255.1, Folder 6)
        [see also McConnell Hall-Foucault's Pendulum]
      - -Construction, 1965 (Box 255.1, Folder 7)
    - -Sketches and Drawings (Architectural and Artistic), undated (Box 255.1, Folder 8)
      [see also Flat File Drawer 9 (Appendix H) for Architectural Plans and oil paintings]
    - Time Capsule, 1967 (Box 255.2)
  - -Engineering Building
    [see Engineering Building]
  - -Proposed Geology Building
    [see Geology Building (Never Built)]
  - -Proposed Science Center, 1946 (Box 255.1, Folder 9)
- Seeger Cottage
  [see Tyler Annex]
- Seelye Hall
  - -General, 1930- (Box 256.1, Folder 10)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1900- (Box 256.1, Folder 11)
    - -Exterior, undated (Box 256.1, Folder 12)
    - -Exterior-Rear View, 1900- (Box 256.1, Folder 13)
    - -Exterior-Special Features, 1976; undated (Box 256.1, Folder 14)
    - -Exterior-With Other Buildings, undated (Box 256.1, Folder 15)
    - -Exterior-With Students, 1980- (Box 256.1, Folder 16)
    - -Exterior (Box 256.1)
    - -Interior-Basement and Kaffee Klatsch, 1900- (Box 256.1, Folder 1)
    - -Interior-Classrooms, 1904- (Box 256.1, Folder 2)
    - -Interior-Halls and Stairs, 1980- (Box 256.1, Folder 3)
    - -Interior-Room 30 / 207, 1904- (Box 256.1, Folder 4)
    - -Interior-Miscellaneous, 1904- (Box 256.1, Folder 5)
- Sessions House
  - -General, 1930-; undated (Box 256.2, Folder 6)
  - -Clippings, 1932-1989 (Box 256.2, Folder 7)
  - -Ghost, 1929- (Box 256.2, Folder 8)
  - -History
    - -General, 1934-1959 (Box 256.2, Folder 9)
    - -General, undated (Box 256.2, Folder 10)
    - -History Scrapbook, 1905
      [see Oversize Box 13 (Appendix H)]
    - -The Hunt / Henshaw House: A Memorial to Colonial Life by Megan Gardner 1998, 1996 (Box 256.2, Folder 11)
    - -The Hunt / Henshaw House-Material, undated (Box 256.2, Folder 12)
    - -The Hunt / Henshaw House-Matieral, undated (Box 256.2, Folder 13)
  - -House Government, 1967- (Box 256.3, Folder 1)
  - -Renovations, 1996 (Box 256.3, Folder 2)
  - -Secret Staircase
    [see Sessions-Ghost and see Sessions-Renovations]
  - -Wallpaper Sample
    [see Flat File Drawer 9 (Appendix H)]
  - -Miscellaneous, 1918- (Box 256.3, Folder 3)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1897- (Box 256.3, Folder 4)
    - -Interior, 1903- (Box 256.3, Folder 5)
    - -Groups, 1903-1945 (Box 256.3, Folder 6)
    - -Groups, 1946-1955 (Box 256.3, Folder 7)
    - -Groups (Album), 1956 (Box 256.3, Folder 8)
    - -Groups (Album), 1957 (Box 256.3, Folder 9)
    - -Groups (Album), 1958 (Box 256.3, Folder 10)
    - -Groups (Album), 1959 (Box 256.3, Folder 11)
    - -Groups, 1960- (Box 256.3, Folder 12)
    - -Groups, undated (Box 256.3, Folder 13)
  - -Sketches and Drawings (Artistic), undated (Box 256.3, Folder 14)
- Sessions House Annex, 1970- (Box 256.3, Folder 15)
- Dr. Seymour's House
  [see Elm St. #79]
- Sheldon House (19 Center Street Avenue), 1898-1901 (Box 256.3, Folder 16)
- The Shop
  [see Gymnasium, Old]
- Snowe House (10 Green Street), 1894-1895 (Box 256.3, Folder 17)
- South Street # 103
  [see the Anchorage]
- Southwick House
  [see also Eleanor Duckett House]
  - -General, 1967- (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - -Photographs-Exterior and Interior, 1889-1905 (Box 257, Folder 2)
  - -Photographs-Groups, 1889-1920 (Box 257, Folder 3)
- Spanish House
  [see Washburn House]
- St. John's Church Parsonage
- Stables
  [see Gymnasium-Equestrian Center]
- Stoddard Hall
  - -General, 1890- (Box 257, Folder 4)
  - -Photographs-Exterior, 1897- (Box 257, Folder 5)
  - -Photographs-Interior, 1901- (Box 257, Folder 6)
- Stoddard House, 1886-1898 (Box 257, Folder 7)
- Student Center
  [see Campus Center]
- Student Clubhouse
  [see Prospect St. # 10]
- Students' Building
  - -General, 1897-1964 (Box 257, Folder 8)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1903-1964 (Box 257, Folder 9)
    - -Exterior, undated (Box 257, Folder 10)
    - -Interior, 1904-1915 (Box 257, Folder 11)
    - -Interior-Theater, 1927-1958 (Box 257, Folder 12)
    - -Groups and Events, 1917-1930 (Box 257, Folder 13)
  - -Sketches and Drawings (Artistic), undated (Box 257, Folder 14)
- Sunnyside-General, 1905- (Box 258, Folder 1)
- Sunnyside-Register / Roster, 1921-1943 (Box 258, Folder 2)
- Talbot House
  - -General, 1953- (Box 258, Folder 3)
  - -Guest Book, 1922-1926 (Box 258, Folder 4)
  - -Register / Roster, 1921-1948; 1951-2 (Box 258, Folder 5)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1921- (Box 258, Folder 6)
    - -Groups, 1922-1955 (Box 258, Folder 7)
    - -Groups, 1956- (Box 258, Folder 8)
- Tenney House 1 (33 Elm Street)
  - -General, 1895- (Box 259, Folder 1)
  - -Round Robin
    - -History, 1950; 1955 (Box 259, Folder 2)
    - -Ashworth, Annie May 1901, 1950-1956 (Box 259, Folder 3)
    - -Batchelder, Alice L. 1901, 1950 (Box 259, Folder 4)
    - -Bradford, Anne Herbert ex-1901 / 1931, 1941-1961 (Box 259, Folder 5)
    - -Cook, Sara Josephine 1900, 1950 (Box 259, Folder 6)
    - -Day, Daisy Toles 1901, undated (Box 259, Folder 7)
    - -DeForest, Sarah Lydia 1901, 1949-1956 (Box 259, Folder 8)
    - -DeForest, Charlotte B. 1901, 1941-1955 (Box 259, Folder 9)
    - -de Long, Ethel Marguerite, 1902 (Box 259, Folder 10)
    - -Drew, Emily Fuller 1903, undated (Box 259, Folder 11)
    - -Dwight, Adelaide Susan 1900, 1947-1953 (Box 259, Folder 12)
    - -Garrison, Fanny, 1961 (Box 259, Folder 13)
    - -Griffith, Mabel Emma, 1903; undated (Box 259, Folder 14)
    - -Hitchcock, Anna Stella 1901, 1950 (Box 259, Folder 15)
    - -Hull, Blanche 1902, 1939 (Box 259, Folder 16)
    - -Kerr, Mina Mahalla 1900, 1947-1958 (Box 259, Folder 17)
    - -Macdonald, Lucy E. 1905, 1903 (Box 259, Folder 18)
    - -Perkins, May Ruth 1900, 1909-1951 (Box 259, Folder 19)
    - -Reed, Clara Everett 1901, 1903-1951 (Box 259, Folder 20)
    - -Sampson, Elizabeth S. 1903, undated (Box 259, Folder 21)
    - -Smith, Sybil Laura 1904, 1904-1909 (Box 259, Folder 22)
    - -Tubby, Gertrude Ogden 1901, 1902-1961 (Box 259, Folder 23)
    - -Yeaw, Fannie Josephine 1901, 1902- (Box 259, Folder 24)
    - -Whittlesley, Dolly Louise 1901, 1907-1961 (Box 259, Folder 25)
    - -Miscellaneous, 1901-1950; undated (Box 259, Folder 26)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1896-1933 (Box 259, Folder 27)
    - -Exterior (Box 259)
    - -Interior, 1891-1893 (Box 259, Folder 28)
    - -Groups, 1896-1936 (Box 259, Folder 29)
- Tenney House 2 (156 Elm Street)
  - -General, 1933- (Box 259, Folder 30)
  - -Architectural Plans
  - -Photographs-Exterior, 1936- (Box 259, Folder 31)
  - -Photographs-Groups, 1936- (Box 259, Folder 32)
- Tilly Hall, 1977- (Box 259, Folder 33)
- Tryon Hall
  [see Museum of Art-Fine Arts Center (-)-Tryon Hall]
- Mrs. / Miss Tucker's
- Tyler House
  - -General, 1898- (Box 260, Folder 1)
  - -50th Anniversary, Feb 15, 1948 (Box 260, Folder 2)
  - -Finances, 1974- (Box 260, Folder 3)
  - -Fire, 1929 (Box 260, Folder 4)
  - -Floor Plan
    [see Oversize Box 12 (Appendix H)]
  - -House Library
    [see Libraries-House-Tyler]
  - -New Student Letters, 1969- (Box 260, Folder 5)
  - -Roster / Register, 1974-1980 (Box 260, Folder 6)
  - -Tylerite News, 1995-1997 (Box 260, Folder 7)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1900- (Box 260, Folder 8)
    - -Interior, 1900- (Box 260, Folder 9)
    - -Groups, 1903- (Box 260, Folder 10)
    - -Norwell House (site of Tyler House), 1895 (Box 260, Folder 11)
  - -Time Capsule not to be opened until 2050, 1998 (Box 260, Folder 41B)
- Tyler House Annex, 1880- (Box 260, Folder 12)
  [see also 12. Distinguished Visitors-Burton, R (Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?)]
- UNITY House, 2000- (Box 260, Folder 13)
- Walker House
- Wallace House
  - -General, 1901-1980 (Box 260, Folder 14)
  - -History, 1922-1953 (Box 260, Folder 15)
  - -Artifacts
  - -Register / Roster, 1923-1959 (Box 260, Folder 16)
  - -Round Robin
  - -Wallace, Rodney, 1903-1971; undated (Box 260, Folder 17)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1892-1959 (Box 260.1, Folder 1)
    - -Exterior, undated (Box 260.1, Folder 2)
    - -Exterior-With Other Buildings, 1904-1953 (Box 260.1, Folder 3)
    - -Interior, 1894-1897 (Box 260.1, Folder 4)
    - -Groups, 1894-1908 (Box 260.1, Folder 5)
    - -Groups, 1916-1954 (Box 260.1, Folder 6)
    - -Groups (Album), 1956-1957 (Box 260.1, Folder 7)
    - -Groups (Album), 1957-1958 (Box 260.1, Folder 8)
    - -Groups (Album), 1958-1959 (Box 260.1, Folder 9)
    - -Groups-Events, 1894-1911 (Box 260.1, Folder 10)
- Washburn House
  - -General, 1932- (Box 261, Folder 1)
  - -History, 1902-1922 (Box 261, Folder 2)
  - -History, 1923-1937 (Box 261, Folder 3)
  - -History, 1938-1944 (Box 261, Folder 4)
  - -Anniversaries, 1928-1978 (Box 261, Folder 5)
  - -House Library
    [see Libraries-House-Washburn]
  - -New Student Handbook, 1961 (Box 261, Folder 6)
  - -Olla Podrida, 1879-1923 (Box 261, Folder 7)
  - -Scrapbook, 1943 (Box 261.1, Folder 8)
  - -Scrapbook, 1987-1988 (Box 261.1, Folder 9)
  - -Scrapbook, 1987-1988 (Box 261.1, Folder 10)
  - -Scrapbook, 1987-1988 (Box 261.1, Folder 11)
  - -Scrapbook, 1938-1939
  - -Scrapbook, 1962-1963
  - -Scrapbook, 1973-1974
    [see Oversize Box 11 (Appendix H)]
  - -Miscellaneous, 1916- (Box 261, Folder 12)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1880-1900 (Box 261.1.1, Folder 1)
    - -Exterior, 1901- (Box 261.1.1, Folder 2)
    - -Exterior-With Other Buildings, 1897-1911 (Box 261.1.1, Folder 3)
    - -Interior, 1890- (Box 261.1.1, Folder 4)
    - -Groups, 1889- (Box 261.1.1, Folder 5)
- Wesley House, 1901- (Box 261.2, Folder 6)
- Wesley House-Scrapbook on Haven / Wesley Greek foster child
- West Street
  - -# 54, 1911-1918 (Box 261.2, Folder 7)
  - -# 57, undated (Box 261.2, Folder 8)
  - -# 62, 1920 (Box 261.2, Folder 9)
  - -# 75, 1912-1918; undated (Box 261.2, Folder 10)
  - -# 83, undated (Box 261.2, Folder 11)
  - -# 101, 1907 (Box 261.2, Folder 12)
  - -# 125 (Physical Plant), 1992- (Box 261.2, Folder 13)
- White House Inn, 1969-1970 (Box 261.2, Folder 14)
  [see also Sessions House Annex]
- White Lodge-General, 1901-1957 (Box 261.2, Folder 15)
- White Lodge-Photographs-Groups, 1899-1921 (Box 261.2, Folder 16)
- Wilder House
  [see also Comstock House, Quadrangle, and Quadrangle-Mandelle]
  - -General, 1930- (Box 261.2, Folder 1)
  - -Bookplate
  - -Government-House President's Notebook, 1968-1982 (Box 261.2, Folder 2)
  - -Government-Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 261.2, Folder 3)
  - -Roster / Register, 1930-1953 (Box 261.2, Folder 4)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1980- (Box 261.2, Folder 5)
    - -Interior, 1930- (Box 261.2, Folder 6)
    - -Groups, 1930- (Box 261.2, Folder 7)
- Wilson House
  [see Martha Wilson House]
- Wright Hall
  - -General, 1959- (Box 262, Folder 8)
  - -Language Lab / Center for Foreign Languages and Cultues (CFLAC), 1961- (Box 262, Folder 9)
  - -Photographs
    - -Construction, 1960-1961 (Box 262, Folder 10)
    - -Exterior-Front View, 1962- (Box 262, Folder 11)
    - -Exterior-Rear View, 1962- (Box 262, Folder 12)
    - -Interior
      - -Auditorium and Lower-Level Hallway, 1965- (Box 262, Folder 13)
      - -Classrooms, Halls, Lounges, 1961- (Box 262, Folder 14)
      - -Language Lab / CFLAC, 1961- (Box 262, Folder 1)
    - -Special Events, 1961 (Box 262, Folder 2)
  - -Sketches, Drawings, and Models (Architectural and Artistic), 1960 (Box 262, Folder 3)
- Yale House, 1988- (Box 262, Folder 4)
- Ziskind House
  [see also Cutter House]
  - -General, 1956- (Box 262, Folder 5)
  - -Ziskind, Jacob, 1956 (Box 262, Folder 6)
  - -Photographs-Exterior and Interior, 1957- (Box 262, Folder 7)
  - -Groups, 1960 (Box 262, Folder 8)